<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Neuronerdz</string>
    <string name="title_activity_explore">Explore</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    <string name="about_us_content"><![CDATA[Welcome to neuronerdz, a bloggers backyard. Neuronerdz is not a mere content providing site, it is that and much more. It is a  backyard full of wonders. We have \'clios cronical\' for history lovers to dig out all the hidden secrets of time. \'Food streat\' is at your service to provide you with timely treats and to indulge your taste buds. Apart from these two gems we also dabble into travel, education, Science and Technology, entertainment etc. We watch the world with nerdz coloured glasses and always have a look out for stories. As we grow we hope to build a place rich in diversified content to appease one and all. So tag along to be in loop and keep exploring the nerd in you.]]></string>
    <string name="about_us_first_para">Neuronerdz is a community of nerdz that wishes to penetrate the blogging culture in India and subsequently the world with a simple goal in mind: To provide fantastic content, curated by the people that most understand their current generation audience. Neuronerdz wishes to create a youthful brand with content emerging from a diverse array of youth across the country and hopefully, one day around the globe.</string>
    <string name="neuronerdz_second_para">Neuronerdz is not a mere content providing site, it is that and much more. It is a backyard full of wonders. We have Clio’s Chronicles for history lovers to dig out all the hidden secrets of time. Food streat is at your service to provide you with timely treats and to indulge your taste buds. Apart from these two gems we also dabble into travel, education, Science and Technology, entertainment etc. We watch the world with nerdz glasses and always have a look out for stories. As we grow we hope to build a place rich in diversified content to appease one and all. So tag along to be in loop and keep exploring the nerd in you.</string>
    <string name="neuronerdz_third_para">While Neuronerdz recognizes it’s goal to provide quality original material as its primary objective it also wishes to create a medium for reliable, accurate and extremely resourceful marketing via its blogging services, hence proving the uniqueness and importance of a youthful organization that is competent in real-world scenarios.</string>
</resources>